savetubevideo.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy - SaveTubeVideo.com

Last updated: June 18, 2018

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

1\. What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

We do not collect personal information from visitors of our site or other details to help you with your experience.

2\. Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

3\. We use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, it won't affect the user's experience.

4\. Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information. Please note that you will be able to use our service and download media files from YouTube only if you are signed in with your Google Account. In this case, SaveTubeVideo may use your personal details through your YouTube account if you have one. That is done with the aim to track data and improve our website performance.

5\. Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:

support@savetubevideo.com
